<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>xv on groupbool</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/authors/xv/</link><description>Recent content in xv on groupbool</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 20:00:19 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://groupbool.xyz/authors/xv/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Tetsuo &amp; Youth</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/tetsuo-and-youth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 20:00:19 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/tetsuo-and-youth/</guid><description/></item><item><title>A Written Testimony</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/a-written-testimony/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 20:06:13 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/a-written-testimony/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Reclaiming Orange</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-01-27-21/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 19:23:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-01-27-21/</guid><description>With the worldwide jubilation at the exodus of the previous administration, I realized the unappetizing cheeto-dust colored skin of the twitter president has tainted the color orange for many of us. This very association of orange with racism and incompetency is what I am here today to begin to dismantle, by reminding us of the beauty and previous symbolism of orange through music:
Larry June’s album Out the Trunk orbits two motifs: citrus and his car.</description></item><item><title>Spooky Serenades</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-10-20/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 19:48:52 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-10-20/</guid><description>As we turn the corner of yet another quarantine month, time feels more like a fantastical construct each day and my household grasps for any ways of distinguishing this month from the last 6. Consequentially, oc and I have been getting into the Halloween spirit more than we normally do (which was already a lot).
Our home is decked out in orange and cobwebs and my playlist has been sprinkled with spooky rap.</description></item><item><title>Drive the Boat</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-05-07/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 23:33:51 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-05-07/</guid><description>One of the oldest motifs in hip hop is Hennessy—ubiquitous in tracks from its inception through today. Rappers laud Hennessy as an aphrodisiac, the fuel for a wild night, a staple in daily life. The golden hue and bottle emulate luxury yet Henny touts an accessibility to listeners and rappers alike. Hennessy accumulated an intense loyalty early on from the hip hop community because it was one of the only companies to hire black executives, and I’ll drink to that 🥂</description></item><item><title/><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-03-19/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 19:33:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-03-19/</guid><description>In a “Fair and Lovely” world where virtually every skincare product in the East is sold with lighteners, the dark skinned people of the world apply those creams, rinses, and even bleaches trying to be “beautiful”; while in parallel their coveted light skinned counterparts slow roast themselves in tanning beds or under the sun with the same goal in mind&amp;hellip; the grass always seems to be greener.
This tritone celebrates the beauty of that darker skin — as a chubby preteen with the darkest skin of all the girls in my family, self esteem was never really in abundance; an experience I regrettably share with countless kids around the world.</description></item><item><title>I got sunshine…</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-02-06/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:35:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-02-06/</guid><description>Music can be a conduit and amplifier for any mood: there are many a meme about listening to sad songs when you’re sad to make you sadder. While their purpose is to provoke a chuckle from a passerby scroller, they hint at a powerful and universal effect music seems to have. Songs enhance, highlight, and even create moods and feelings.
Revisiting the idea of leaning on music when you’re feeling down, these three songs are my essentials for any rainy day.</description></item><item><title>Time Travel in Pink</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-01-02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 21:27:07 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-01-02/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-12-12/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 22:51:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-12-12/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Melii</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/melii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:01:45 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/melii/</guid><description>The second spanish baddie to be highlighted on groupbool: Melii stuns with both looks and lyricism.
My love for this artist stems from her seamless transitioning: singing to rapping, english to spanish and back again. She weaves between styles gracefully and fluidly, no small feat for a 20 year old. Raised in Harlem, Melii was smooched by the limelight for the first time on Meek Mill&amp;rsquo;s album *Championships.*However, since then she has proven herself hella versatile and way more than a random feature:</description></item><item><title>Meek Mill</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/meek-mill/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:01:45 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/meek-mill/</guid><description>When I first heard Meek Mill, I dismissed him as a non-unique, cookie cutter, misogynistic rapper that didn’t really bring anything new to the table and the only thing I knew about him is that he beefed with Drake. His voice was just so yell-ey and hard to digest because it felt more like he was chastising me than spitting bars.
HOWEVER, I feel v differently now! I want u guys to give him a chance too.</description></item></channel></rss>