<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sp on groupbool</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/authors/sp/</link><description>Recent content in sp on groupbool</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 18:28:24 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://groupbool.xyz/authors/sp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>wagwan bruv</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-10-08/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 18:28:24 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-10-08/</guid><description>The novel coronavirus has brought upon an unexpected shift to our way of life. The squad hasn’t even met in close to six months. We’ve all been fortunate enough to continue working from home however the lack of boundaries had made me feel more like a corporate drone lately. Day in and day out, it’s almost like we’re living a groundhog day scenario. This pandemic isn’t so much to blame but it has managed to compound my absurdist outlook.</description></item><item><title>Fuck Me Pumps / Gold Digger</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/f-me-pumps-gold-digger/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 18:42:30 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/f-me-pumps-gold-digger/</guid><description>That part never goes right “Fuck Me Pumps” is a track off of Amy Winehoue’s debut album, Frank. With an upbeat melody and a catchy rhythm, Amy uses humorous and clever wordplay to deliver a grounded but harsh glimpse into what we conventionally identify as gold digging women.
Amy has the perspective of an outsider looking into the lives of these women. The track is a barrage of shortcomings that these women possess as they attempt to capture the high life but somehow they always seem to fall short.</description></item><item><title>Shakespearean Sorrows</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-03-12/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 23:21:40 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-03-12/</guid><description>Shakespeare is revered for the universality of his themes that break geographic and class barriers. Even after 400 years, high schoolers everywhere can’t seem to shake his presence. His works are avidly studied and his themes manage to show up in the most unexpected places. The bard’s 16th century writing might seem like the furthest thing away from hip-hop but lately I’ve been hearing references to complex Shakespearean characters in very clever ways.</description></item><item><title>Sadbois Need Love</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/sadbois-need-love/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 10:48:59 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/sadbois-need-love/</guid><description>The term sadboi has been taking hold within groupbool for some time now. It all started when pb was intervened by several people within the span of his bi-monthly blonde listening sessions. He elaborated this encounter further on his blog but in summary, he was defensive about being called a sadboi and went to great lengths to empirically prove that he&amp;rsquo;s not. However that situation got me wondering, aren&amp;rsquo;t we all sadbois in some respects, albeit some more than others?</description></item><item><title>leggo my lagos</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-02-06/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 22:36:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-02-06/</guid><description>On the coast of West Africa lies Nigeria, one of the populous countries in the world. It is an economic powerhouse with an emerging market that is on track to become a global super power. On top of this, Nigeria also has an incredible music scene with a cultural lineage that goes way back; from being at the forefront of early highlife to playing a major role in the development of afrobeat with the likes of the legendary Fela Kuti.</description></item><item><title>uncut gems</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-01-16/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 23:38:06 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-01-16/</guid><description>One of my favorite aspects of hip hop has to be its versatility. It is capable of fluidly traversing genres and make unconventional pairings sound right at home. This mostly speaks to a producer’s mixing prowess but also to the ability of the artist to supplement the original sample whether in relation to the subject matter or the sound itself. The artist is not simply using the sample as sonic filler but rather as an homage&amp;mdash;paying tribute to another as a jumping off point to their own ends.</description></item><item><title>body and soul</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-01-02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 20:11:44 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-01-02/</guid><description>The world will never see another Amy Winehouse again, she was one of a kind with unparalleled talent and musicality. Her emotional depth and her ability to convey deep and personal subject matters while fluidly traversing genre boundaries was other worldly. Although she left this world too soon, she left behind an incredible legacy. I keep finding artists that embody her musical spirit in both tone and subject matter and it always leaves me a little bit emotional.</description></item><item><title>sound discovery</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-12-19/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:32:29 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-12-19/</guid><description/></item><item><title>stark honesty</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-12-12/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 22:04:49 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-12-12/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The Drake Dilemma</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/the-drake-dilemma/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:48:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/the-drake-dilemma/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a running joke among the squad whenever one of us has Drake show up on the gb feed. We see it as a guilty pleasure that has finally been shoved into the spotlight for the rest of squad to see. Ok it&amp;rsquo;s not that dramatic and it&amp;rsquo;s not I don&amp;rsquo;t like Drake as an artist. However some of the squad members (xv and oc) get very defensive when we point it out, thus making the situation hilarious.</description></item><item><title>jadedAtTwentyTwo</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/albums/jadedattwentytwo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 23:08:45 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/albums/jadedattwentytwo/</guid><description>To my day one boolers, who&amp;rsquo;ve been booling with me through and through, here&amp;rsquo;s a mixtape bool.
A brief experiment with sampling some of my records and playing around with editing audio. Start from the beginning and use headphones.</description></item><item><title>summer</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/summer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 11:36:18 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/summer/</guid><description>A season characterized by warm weather, good vibes and a distinct lack of seasonal affective disorder. I genuinely think that people can be circumstantially shown to be happier during the summer time.
This idea starts when we are too young to actualize the world, in the form of long and blissful breaks. Months of free time without the encumbrance of school. Free time to sit around, explore ourselves and discover new relationships.</description></item><item><title>Joy Crookes</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/joy-crookes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 23:30:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/joy-crookes/</guid><description>I’ve got an interesting artist for you guys today: Joy Crookes, a 20 year old up and coming singer songwriter from the UK. The first thing that caught me off guard was the tone of her voice, a huskiness that parallels Amy and Lauryn, with a jazzy bend calling back to the likes of Eartha Kitt.
I wanted to look at two songs off of her EP Reminiscence. As the title insinuates, this EP revolves around love lost and lost love.</description></item></channel></rss>