<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>groupbool</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/</link><description>Recent content on groupbool</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 16:29:27 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://groupbool.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Reclaiming Orange</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-01-27-21/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 19:23:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-01-27-21/</guid><description>With the worldwide jubilation at the exodus of the previous administration, I realized the unappetizing cheeto-dust colored skin of the twitter president has tainted the color orange for many of us. This very association of orange with racism and incompetency is what I am here today to begin to dismantle, by reminding us of the beauty and previous symbolism of orange through music:
Larry June’s album Out the Trunk orbits two motifs: citrus and his car.</description></item><item><title>Suspension of Disbelief</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-11-19-2020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 21:43:04 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-11-19-2020/</guid><description>Imagine immersing yourself in a 1940&amp;rsquo;s biopic and the main character listens to K-pop all throughout the movie - sounds ridiculous right? Period pieces rely heavily on the soundtrack for immersion. The sounds of a movie set the auditory backdrop and allow you to fully engross yourself in the time period. With that being said, when the music starkly clashes with the time period, I find my attention fully focused on the character and their actions.</description></item><item><title>straight outta atl</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-11-11-20/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 19:53:52 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-11-11-20/</guid><description>Despite the east coast provenance of the hip hop scene, the southern lab has established itself as the genre&amp;rsquo;s powerhouse multiple times over the hop hop timeline. More recently, the trap artists coming out of ATL have taken the world by storm and finally cemented rap as the mainstream sound. 1
Trap&amp;rsquo;s signature sound has found a wide following all over the world. It is creating a legacy that is uniquely its own withing the context of the artist&amp;rsquo;s circumstances and social context.</description></item><item><title>Spooky Serenades</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-10-20/</link><pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 19:48:52 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-10-20/</guid><description>As we turn the corner of yet another quarantine month, time feels more like a fantastical construct each day and my household grasps for any ways of distinguishing this month from the last 6. Consequentially, oc and I have been getting into the Halloween spirit more than we normally do (which was already a lot).
Our home is decked out in orange and cobwebs and my playlist has been sprinkled with spooky rap.</description></item><item><title>wagwan bruv</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-10-08/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 18:28:24 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-10-08/</guid><description>The novel coronavirus has brought upon an unexpected shift to our way of life. The squad hasn’t even met in close to six months. We’ve all been fortunate enough to continue working from home however the lack of boundaries had made me feel more like a corporate drone lately. Day in and day out, it’s almost like we’re living a groundhog day scenario. This pandemic isn’t so much to blame but it has managed to compound my absurdist outlook.</description></item><item><title>Lessons in Bending</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-06-11/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 15:34:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-06-11/</guid><description>Netflix released Avatar: The Last Airbender onto their streaming platform last month, and it couldn’t have come at a better time—providing the perfect quarantine escape and touching on social plagues that have spanned generations. Finishing the series last weekend with my fellow boolers left me with every emotion, including the desire to bend elements. While water, earth, fire, and air bending are obviously not achievable in our physical world, they have plenty of familiar roots that can be tapped into.</description></item><item><title>American Music</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/jb-06-11/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:06:01 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/jb-06-11/</guid><description>Amiri Baraka said it best: “One of the most baffling things about America is that despite its essentially vile profile, so much beauty continues to exist here. Perhaps it’s as so many thinkers have said, that it is because of the vileness, or call it adversity, that such beauty does exist. (As balance?)”.
American music is black music. Listen, feel, and understand.</description></item><item><title>Su Lee</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/mg-06-05/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 19:00:11 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/mg-06-05/</guid><description>The power of an artist is to feel the ailments of society and diagnose it before we even realize what’s going on. With all that&amp;rsquo;s going on in the world, Su Lee is the sonic physician we all need right now. Her song &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ll Just Dance&amp;rdquo; was a viral hit on YouTube partly because of her dancing in her bedroom studio, but also because she was able to put to words the vibes of this crazy year and make us feel okay with it for once.</description></item><item><title>Drive the Boat</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-05-07/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2020 23:33:51 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-05-07/</guid><description>One of the oldest motifs in hip hop is Hennessy—ubiquitous in tracks from its inception through today. Rappers laud Hennessy as an aphrodisiac, the fuel for a wild night, a staple in daily life. The golden hue and bottle emulate luxury yet Henny touts an accessibility to listeners and rappers alike. Hennessy accumulated an intense loyalty early on from the hip hop community because it was one of the only companies to hire black executives, and I’ll drink to that 🥂</description></item><item><title>F Me Pumps / Gold Digger</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/f-me-pumps-gold-digger/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 18:42:30 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/f-me-pumps-gold-digger/</guid><description>That part never goes right “Fuck Me Pumps” is a track off of Amy Winehoue’s debut album, Frank. With an upbeat melody and a catchy rhythm, Amy uses humorous and clever wordplay to deliver a grounded but harsh glimpse into what we conventionally identify as gold digging women.
Amy has the perspective of an outsider looking into the lives of these women. The track is a barrage of shortcomings that these women possess as they attempt to capture the high life but somehow they always seem to fall short.</description></item><item><title>Procaine hydrochloride</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-04-02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 21:43:04 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-04-02/</guid><description>In these frantic times, you might walk through your drug store aisles, looking for Tylenol or Advil. You&amp;rsquo;ll walk by bare shelves and realize that everyone else cleared out the stock in a panic. Now there&amp;rsquo;s no reason to be upset—hidden away in the bottom shelf, you&amp;rsquo;ll find Acetaminophen and Ibuprofen. They&amp;rsquo;re generic versions of those medications, but they&amp;rsquo;re just as effective. They might not have the eye catching marketing or the superior effectiveness we&amp;rsquo;ve been placebo&amp;rsquo;d into believing.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-03-19/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 19:33:34 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-03-19/</guid><description>In a “Fair and Lovely” world where virtually every skincare product in the East is sold with lighteners, the dark skinned people of the world apply those creams, rinses, and even bleaches trying to be “beautiful”; while in parallel their coveted light skinned counterparts slow roast themselves in tanning beds or under the sun with the same goal in mind&amp;hellip; the grass always seems to be greener.
This tritone celebrates the beauty of that darker skin — as a chubby preteen with the darkest skin of all the girls in my family, self esteem was never really in abundance; an experience I regrettably share with countless kids around the world.</description></item><item><title>Shakespearean Sorrows</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-03-12/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 23:21:40 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-03-12/</guid><description>Shakespeare is revered for the universality of his themes that break geographic and class barriers. Even after 400 years, high schoolers everywhere can’t seem to shake his presence. His works are avidly studied and his themes manage to show up in the most unexpected places. The bard’s 16th century writing might seem like the furthest thing away from hip-hop but lately I’ve been hearing references to complex Shakespearean characters in very clever ways.</description></item><item><title>Sadbois Need Love</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/sadbois-need-love/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2020 10:48:59 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/sadbois-need-love/</guid><description>The term sadboi has been taking hold within groupbool for some time now. It all started when pb was intervened by several people within the span of his bi-monthly blonde listening sessions. He elaborated this encounter further on his blog but in summary, he was defensive about being called a sadboi and went to great lengths to empirically prove that he&amp;rsquo;s not. However that situation got me wondering, aren&amp;rsquo;t we all sadbois in some respects, albeit some more than others?</description></item><item><title>leggo my lagos</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-02-06/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 22:36:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-02-06/</guid><description>On the coast of West Africa lies Nigeria, one of the populous countries in the world. It is an economic powerhouse with an emerging market that is on track to become a global super power. On top of this, Nigeria also has an incredible music scene with a cultural lineage that goes way back; from being at the forefront of early highlife to playing a major role in the development of afrobeat with the likes of the legendary Fela Kuti.</description></item><item><title>Time &amp; Space</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-02-06/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 22:36:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-02-06/</guid><description>Different people measure time in different ways. Birthdays, milestones, relationships, jobs etc. For me, over the past several years, time is measured by Spotify playlists. Each playlist of mine is a time capsule that holds memories stirred by each song that comes on shuffle when I revisit it months, or even years later. Music is beautiful and powerful in that way. Below are three songs, each from a different playlist, that bring back only the happiest memories.</description></item><item><title>I got sunshine…</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-02-06/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 00:35:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-02-06/</guid><description>Music can be a conduit and amplifier for any mood: there are many a meme about listening to sad songs when you’re sad to make you sadder. While their purpose is to provoke a chuckle from a passerby scroller, they hint at a powerful and universal effect music seems to have. Songs enhance, highlight, and even create moods and feelings.
Revisiting the idea of leaning on music when you’re feeling down, these three songs are my essentials for any rainy day.</description></item><item><title>uncut gems</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-01-16/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 23:38:06 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-01-16/</guid><description>One of my favorite aspects of hip hop has to be its versatility. It is capable of fluidly traversing genres and make unconventional pairings sound right at home. This mostly speaks to a producer’s mixing prowess but also to the ability of the artist to supplement the original sample whether in relation to the subject matter or the sound itself. The artist is not simply using the sample as sonic filler but rather as an homage&amp;mdash;paying tribute to another as a jumping off point to their own ends.</description></item><item><title>Bollywood Bangers</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-01-16/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 23:16:26 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-01-16/</guid><description>Bollywood frequently gets written off as a second rate film industry - and for good reason. Most movies are poorly written and laughably acted cashgrabs. But every few years, a new movie comes out that equals if not surpasses Hollywood quality blockbusters. In my opinion, no director is better at producing these films than Sanjay Leela Banshali. His movies draw from epic periods in Indian history (albeit with a good bit of fictionalization and bias).</description></item><item><title>Tat on my ribs like—</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-01-09/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 21:33:47 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-01-09/</guid><description>I do not know what permanent is.
The artist behind each of these tracks has stolen my dream of Drake tattooing their likeness onto his body—as each have achieved a level of talent or fame worthy of him abandoning the will of his Jewish God to homage.
Sade’s otherworldliness has earned her not one but two placements on Drake’s physical being—given her beauty and the influence of her sensual sound on tracks such as “I Couldn’t Love You More”.</description></item><item><title>mom's spaghetti</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-01-09/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 08:08:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-01-09/</guid><description>Its hard to relate on a personal level with rappers; most people don&amp;rsquo;t live through the same experiences that inspire these artists&amp;rsquo; music. But its easy to empathize with the sincerity in their words when they write about their moms. Three artists from different eras with different styles that rap about wildly different topics. One consistent theme - their songs about their respective moms are some of their best.
Reminder to call your mom if you haven&amp;rsquo;t in a while.</description></item><item><title>Time Travel in Pink</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-01-02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 21:27:07 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-01-02/</guid><description/></item><item><title>body and soul</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-01-02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 20:11:44 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-01-02/</guid><description>The world will never see another Amy Winehouse again, she was one of a kind with unparalleled talent and musicality. Her emotional depth and her ability to convey deep and personal subject matters while fluidly traversing genre boundaries was other worldly. Although she left this world too soon, she left behind an incredible legacy. I keep finding artists that embody her musical spirit in both tone and subject matter and it always leaves me a little bit emotional.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-12-19/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:40:08 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-12-19/</guid><description/></item><item><title>sound discovery</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-12-19/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:32:29 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-12-19/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-12-12/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 22:51:09 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/xv-12-12/</guid><description/></item><item><title>stark honesty</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-12-12/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 22:04:49 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/sp-12-12/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The Drake Dilemma</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/the-drake-dilemma/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 20:48:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/the-drake-dilemma/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s a running joke among the squad whenever one of us has Drake show up on the gb feed. We see it as a guilty pleasure that has finally been shoved into the spotlight for the rest of squad to see. Ok it&amp;rsquo;s not that dramatic and it&amp;rsquo;s not I don&amp;rsquo;t like Drake as an artist. However some of the squad members (xv and oc) get very defensive when we point it out, thus making the situation hilarious.</description></item><item><title>Melii</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/melii/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 00:01:45 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/melii/</guid><description>The second spanish baddie to be highlighted on groupbool: Melii stuns with both looks and lyricism.
My love for this artist stems from her seamless transitioning: singing to rapping, english to spanish and back again. She weaves between styles gracefully and fluidly, no small feat for a 20 year old. Raised in Harlem, Melii was smooched by the limelight for the first time on Meek Mill&amp;rsquo;s album *Championships.*However, since then she has proven herself hella versatile and way more than a random feature:</description></item><item><title>jadedAtTwentyTwo</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/albums/jadedattwentytwo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 23:08:45 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/albums/jadedattwentytwo/</guid><description>To my day one boolers, who&amp;rsquo;ve been booling with me through and through, here&amp;rsquo;s a mixtape bool.
A brief experiment with sampling some of my records and playing around with editing audio. Start from the beginning and use headphones.</description></item><item><title>Higher Brothers</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/higher-brothers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/higher-brothers/</guid><description>Higher Brothers (MaSiWei, DZ, Psy.P, Melo), a chinese hip hop group, collaborate with Florida rappers, Ski Mask the Slump God and Denzel Curry on &amp;ldquo;One Punch Man&amp;rdquo;. Ski Mask and Denzel have been known to make references to anime in their own works and this has become a growing motif reaching a full swell with the rise of SoundCloud rap. The late XXXTentacion is a quintessential example of this idea and the magnitude of his impact on the younger generation of rap listeners is indisputable.</description></item><item><title>Rosalía pt. 1</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/rosalia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/rosalia/</guid><description>Every few years there&amp;rsquo;s a new wave of artists that steamrolls the music industry. A handful of artists make it big: they garner a viral following, they sell out shows, and they make millions. Then there&amp;rsquo;s one artist out of the handful that revolutionizes music. We play their songs over and over again, chasing the adrenaline that sweeps us when they take the stage. Their music is like acoustic opioids, and we return to it time after time to make us truly feel something.</description></item><item><title>summer</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/summer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 11:36:18 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/summer/</guid><description>A season characterized by warm weather, good vibes and a distinct lack of seasonal affective disorder. I genuinely think that people can be circumstantially shown to be happier during the summer time.
This idea starts when we are too young to actualize the world, in the form of long and blissful breaks. Months of free time without the encumbrance of school. Free time to sit around, explore ourselves and discover new relationships.</description></item><item><title>feed</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/feed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 16:29:27 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/feed/</guid><description>squad bumps</description></item><item><title>Ari Lennox</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/ari-lennox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/ari-lennox/</guid><description>My trip with xv to Dreamville Fest this past weekend is inspiration for today’s artist of the week… Ari Lennox! The only female artist signed with J. Cole. Inarguably (xv won’t argue) the most talented and stacked label in the game right now, Ari holds her own and she proved that to me this weekend.
Ari’s someone I’ve respected for a few years now, since I was introduced to her sound on Revenge of the Dreamers II.</description></item><item><title>Meek Mill</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/meek-mill/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:01:45 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/meek-mill/</guid><description>When I first heard Meek Mill, I dismissed him as a non-unique, cookie cutter, misogynistic rapper that didn’t really bring anything new to the table and the only thing I knew about him is that he beefed with Drake. His voice was just so yell-ey and hard to digest because it felt more like he was chastising me than spitting bars.
HOWEVER, I feel v differently now! I want u guys to give him a chance too.</description></item><item><title>Joy Crookes</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/joy-crookes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2019 23:30:25 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/joy-crookes/</guid><description>I’ve got an interesting artist for you guys today: Joy Crookes, a 20 year old up and coming singer songwriter from the UK. The first thing that caught me off guard was the tone of her voice, a huskiness that parallels Amy and Lauryn, with a jazzy bend calling back to the likes of Eartha Kitt.
I wanted to look at two songs off of her EP Reminiscence. As the title insinuates, this EP revolves around love lost and lost love.</description></item></channel></rss>