<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jgb on groupbool</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/authors/jgb/</link><description>Recent content in jgb on groupbool</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 17:18:46 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://groupbool.xyz/authors/jgb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I KNOW VIBRATIONS</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/jgb-12-22-2022/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 17:18:46 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/jgb-12-22-2022/</guid><description>“I KNOW VIBRATIONS” in white text on an orange t-shirt. Someone make this and gift it to Laraaji next time he’s in town. When the man himself came to Creative Alliance, he navigated a gong like I’ve never felt before. Right hand melded with mallet, left with directional mic, he was the moon’s pull to that gong’s ocean. At this concert Laraaji encouraged spectators to cozy up by bringing blankets and pillows to the show, Tagarp schoolhouse style.</description></item><item><title>Island Smarts</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/jgb-11-25-21/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 12:15:42 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/jgb-11-25-21/</guid><description>We all know about the classic debate about book smarts and street smarts. Allow me to introduce a third contender: island smarts. But first, a quick digression: Ben Taylor has a great episode of his podcast Thinking Basketball where he talks about the tyranny of the quantifiable as it relates to the limitation of using analytics for basketball decision making. Tyranny of the quantifiable is the tendency for people to give preference to measurable factors in any given situation at the expense of perhaps more important, but difficult to quantify factors.</description></item><item><title>No Limit</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/no-limit/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 19:57:42 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/no-limit/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s my story of yesterday
tm told me about the no limit reunion tour at the Daughters of the American Revolution concert hall, so I&amp;rsquo;m naturally down just because rap in that building is super silly. I didnt look up anything about the group and little did I know that this was the most hood rap I can think of. Just so much bass. Unimaginable bass. I&amp;rsquo;m not exaggerating at all when I say this, I heard the music from 2 blocks away.</description></item><item><title>13th Month</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/kelman-duran-13th-month/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 20:15:04 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/kelman-duran-13th-month/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Tetsuo &amp; Youth</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/tetsuo-and-youth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 20:00:19 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/tetsuo-and-youth/</guid><description/></item><item><title>A Written Testimony</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/a-written-testimony/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 20:06:13 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/a-written-testimony/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Charge</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/hr-charge/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:18:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/hr-charge/</guid><description/></item><item><title>The Shape of Jazz Which Came</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/jgb-02-04-21/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/jgb-02-04-21/</guid><description>Alright, so I know we&amp;rsquo;re trying to be approachable and not pretentious here, but indulge me for a moment.
In &amp;ldquo;The Shape of Jazz to Come&amp;rdquo; (1959, Atlantic), Ornette Coleman presents a nascent vision of the unburdened musicality which will become the revolutionary &amp;ldquo;free jazz&amp;rdquo; movement (although the producers added a self-imposed burden with that album title - quite a claim). Coleman&amp;rsquo;s vision is a musical system apart from traditional (read: Western) tonal centers and consonant harmonies where the musicians&amp;rsquo; individuality and voice is put to the forefront to be compared and complimented by their fellow improvisors.</description></item><item><title>Al Oud: Instruments &amp; Vocal Music</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/al-oud-hamza-el-din/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 20:52:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/recordclub/al-oud-hamza-el-din/</guid><description/></item><item><title>American Music</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/jgb-06-11/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:06:01 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/jgb-06-11/</guid><description>Amiri Baraka said it best: “One of the most baffling things about America is that despite its essentially vile profile, so much beauty continues to exist here. Perhaps it’s as so many thinkers have said, that it is because of the vileness, or call it adversity, that such beauty does exist. (As balance?)”.
American music is black music. Listen, feel, and understand.</description></item></channel></rss>