<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>oc on groupbool</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/authors/oc/</link><description>Recent content in oc on groupbool</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 15:34:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://groupbool.xyz/authors/oc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lessons in Bending</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-06-11/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 15:34:08 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-06-11/</guid><description>Netflix released Avatar: The Last Airbender onto their streaming platform last month, and it couldn’t have come at a better time—providing the perfect quarantine escape and touching on social plagues that have spanned generations. Finishing the series last weekend with my fellow boolers left me with every emotion, including the desire to bend elements. While water, earth, fire, and air bending are obviously not achievable in our physical world, they have plenty of familiar roots that can be tapped into.</description></item><item><title>Time &amp; Space</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-02-06/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 22:36:51 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-02-06/</guid><description>Different people measure time in different ways. Birthdays, milestones, relationships, jobs etc. For me, over the past several years, time is measured by Spotify playlists. Each playlist of mine is a time capsule that holds memories stirred by each song that comes on shuffle when I revisit it months, or even years later. Music is beautiful and powerful in that way. Below are three songs, each from a different playlist, that bring back only the happiest memories.</description></item><item><title>Tat on my ribs like—</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-01-09/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 21:33:47 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-01-09/</guid><description>I do not know what permanent is.
The artist behind each of these tracks has stolen my dream of Drake tattooing their likeness onto his body—as each have achieved a level of talent or fame worthy of him abandoning the will of his Jewish God to homage.
Sade’s otherworldliness has earned her not one but two placements on Drake’s physical being—given her beauty and the influence of her sensual sound on tracks such as “I Couldn’t Love You More”.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-12-19/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 00:40:08 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/oc-12-19/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Ari Lennox</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/ari-lennox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/ari-lennox/</guid><description>My trip with xv to Dreamville Fest this past weekend is inspiration for today’s artist of the week… Ari Lennox! The only female artist signed with J. Cole. Inarguably (xv won’t argue) the most talented and stacked label in the game right now, Ari holds her own and she proved that to me this weekend.
Ari’s someone I’ve respected for a few years now, since I was introduced to her sound on Revenge of the Dreamers II.</description></item></channel></rss>