<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>pb on groupbool</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/authors/pb/</link><description>Recent content in pb on groupbool</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 23:16:26 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://groupbool.xyz/authors/pb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advertunes</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-02-25-21/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 23:16:26 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-02-25-21/</guid><description>Do you remember the Kia commercials with the hamsters? There&amp;rsquo;s something weirdly sticky about those commercials - they defy logic, and don&amp;rsquo;t make much sense in the context of selling the car but damn do they engrain the brand in your brain for years, decades at this point.
This tritone&amp;rsquo;s songs were all featured in commercials that I saw years ago. None of the commercials really made sense, but I still can&amp;rsquo;t get the tune and the brand out of my brain after all these years.</description></item><item><title>Suspension of Disbelief</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-11-19-2020/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Nov 2020 21:43:04 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-11-19-2020/</guid><description>Imagine immersing yourself in a 1940&amp;rsquo;s biopic and the main character listens to K-pop all throughout the movie - sounds ridiculous right? Period pieces rely heavily on the soundtrack for immersion. The sounds of a movie set the auditory backdrop and allow you to fully engross yourself in the time period. With that being said, when the music starkly clashes with the time period, I find my attention fully focused on the character and their actions.</description></item><item><title>Procaine hydrochloride</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-04-02/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2020 21:43:04 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-04-02/</guid><description>In these frantic times, you might walk through your drug store aisles, looking for Tylenol or Advil. You&amp;rsquo;ll walk by bare shelves and realize that everyone else cleared out the stock in a panic. Now there&amp;rsquo;s no reason to be upset—hidden away in the bottom shelf, you&amp;rsquo;ll find Acetaminophen and Ibuprofen. They&amp;rsquo;re generic versions of those medications, but they&amp;rsquo;re just as effective. They might not have the eye catching marketing or the superior effectiveness we&amp;rsquo;ve been placebo&amp;rsquo;d into believing.</description></item><item><title>Bollywood Bangers</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-01-16/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 23:16:26 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-01-16/</guid><description>Bollywood frequently gets written off as a second rate film industry - and for good reason. Most movies are poorly written and laughably acted cashgrabs. But every few years, a new movie comes out that equals if not surpasses Hollywood quality blockbusters. In my opinion, no director is better at producing these films than Sanjay Leela Banshali. His movies draw from epic periods in Indian history (albeit with a good bit of fictionalization and bias).</description></item><item><title>mom's spaghetti</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-01-09/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 08:08:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/tritones/pb-01-09/</guid><description>Its hard to relate on a personal level with rappers; most people don&amp;rsquo;t live through the same experiences that inspire these artists&amp;rsquo; music. But its easy to empathize with the sincerity in their words when they write about their moms. Three artists from different eras with different styles that rap about wildly different topics. One consistent theme - their songs about their respective moms are some of their best.
Reminder to call your mom if you haven&amp;rsquo;t in a while.</description></item><item><title>Rosalía pt. 1</title><link>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/rosalia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://groupbool.xyz/posts/rosalia/</guid><description>Every few years there&amp;rsquo;s a new wave of artists that steamrolls the music industry. A handful of artists make it big: they garner a viral following, they sell out shows, and they make millions. Then there&amp;rsquo;s one artist out of the handful that revolutionizes music. We play their songs over and over again, chasing the adrenaline that sweeps us when they take the stage. Their music is like acoustic opioids, and we return to it time after time to make us truly feel something.</description></item></channel></rss>